so we have seen that in cycle 13 this
instruction commits it commits by
depositing the value of four into
register r2 looking at the aerobie entry
for r2 to see whether it points to it
and it does and thus we make that entry
in the right point to the register file
and freeing the Rob entry now we will
consider what happens in cycle 14 this
instruction will write the result in
cycle 16 this instruction is an ad it
executes in 13 and writes the result in
14 the question for you is does the rat
any entry change so for example if you
believe that the right entry for our one
is going to change then write our one
here so which rat entry changes as the
result of writing this value for Rob six
instruction